National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Case Files, 1988-2006, Undated; nam_apap298-1; 12.55 cubic ft.
  - Adults, 1988-2006, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1; 9 cubic ft.
    - Hamilton, Michael (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_516 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Hammer, David Paul (FED), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_517 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Hammond, Jerry (AL), 1995; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_518 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Hampton, Lloyd W. (IL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_519 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Haney, Judy (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_520 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Hannibal, Sheldon (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_521 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Hansen, Tracy A. (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_522 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Harden, Donald Eugene (AZ) Executed April 6, 1992, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_523 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Hardwick, John Gary (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_524 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Harries, Ron (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_525 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Harris III, Benjamin J. (WA), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_526 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Harris, David (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_527 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Harris, George B. (MO), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_528 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Harris, James A. (IN), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_529 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Harris, Kenneth Bernard (TX) Executed June 3, 1997, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_530 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Harris, Louise (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_531 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Harvey Jr. Harold Lee (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_532 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Haskett, Randy (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_533 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Hatch, Steven (OK), 1996; nam_apap298-1.1_534 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Hawkins, Jeffrey (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_535 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Hawkins, Samuel (TX) Executed February 21, 1995, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_536 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Hawkins, Thomas (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_537 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Hays, Henry F. (AL), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_538 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Heath, Ronald P. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_539 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Hedlund, Michael (AZ), 2002; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_540 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Heidnik, Gary (PA), 1997; 1999; 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_541 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Heiselbetz, Earl (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_542 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Heishman, Harvey Lee (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_543 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Henderson, Jerome (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_544 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Henderson, Jerry Paul (AL), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_545 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Henderson, Wilbur A. (AR), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_546 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Henry, John (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_547 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Henry, Robert L. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_548 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Henry, Josoph (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_549 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Herman, David Lee (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_550 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Hernandez, Francis (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_551 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Hernandez, Rodolfo (TX), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_552 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Herrera, William Sr. (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_553 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Hicks, David (TX), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_554 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Hill, Clarence E. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_555 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Hill, Darrel (AR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_556 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Hill, Donetta (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_557 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Hill, Mack (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_558 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Hill, Michael (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_559 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Hill, Paul (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_560 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Hinton, Eric Lamot (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_561 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Hitchcock, James E. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_562 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Hittle, Daniel (TX), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_563 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Hochstein, Peter (NE), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_564 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Hodge, Benny Lee (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_565 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Hodges, Henry Eugene (TN(, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_566 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Hoffner, Timothy (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_567 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Hogue, Jerry Lee (TX), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_568 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Hoke Sr., Ronald (VA), 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_569 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Holladay, Glenn (AL), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_570 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Holland, Gerald James (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_571 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Holland, William (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_572 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Holloway, Arnold (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_573 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Holloway, Allen (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_574 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Holloway, Duane (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_575 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Holmes, James Williams (AR) Executed August 3, 1994, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_576 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Holmes, Karl (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_577 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Holton, Daryl (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_578 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Hood, Charles (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_579 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Hooper, Courtney (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_580 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hooper, George (TX), 1991; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_581 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Houston, Eric (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_582 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Hovarter, Jackie Ray (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_583 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Hovey, Richard (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_584 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Howard, Alphonso (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_585 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Howard, Gary Lee (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_586 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Howard, Melvin K. (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_587 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Howard, Ronald (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_588 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Howard, Stacey Dean (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_589 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Hoyos, Jamie Armando (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_590 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Hudson, Timothy C. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_591 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Huggins, Michael (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_592 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Hughes, Billy George (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_593 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Hughes, Preston (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_594 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Hughes, Robert 4th (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_595 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Hunt, Diedre (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_596 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Hunt, Gregory (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_597 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Hunt, Henry (NC), 2003; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_598 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Hunt, Flint (MD), 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_599 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Hurles, Richard (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_600 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Hude, David O'Neal (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_601 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Ibarra, Ramiro Rubi (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_602 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Ingram, Nicky (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_603 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Isa, Marie (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_604 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Isaazs, Carl (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_605 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Jablonski, Phillip (CA), 1994; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_606 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Jackson, Andrea (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_607 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Jackson, Earl (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_608 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Jackson, Etheria V. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_609 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Jackson, Henry Curtis Jr. (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_610 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Jackson, Michael Anthony (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_611 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Jackson, Noel (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_612 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Jackson, Robert W. (DE), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_613 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Jackson, Tommy (TX), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_614 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - James, Antonio (LA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_615 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - James, Terrance (OK), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_616 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Jasper, Alfred (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_617 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Jeffers, Jim (AZ), 1994; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_618 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Jenkins, Daniel Steven (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_619 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Jenkins, Mark (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_620 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Jennings, Bryan (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_621 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Jennings, Michael Wayne (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_622 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Jennings, Wilbur (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_623 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Jermyn, Frederic (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_624 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Johns, Stephen K. (MO), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_625 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Johnsen, Brian David (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_626 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Johnson, Carl (TX) Executed September 19, 1995, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_627 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Johnson, David (AR), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_628 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Johnson, Don (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_629 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Johnson, Dorsie Lee (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_630 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Johnson, Edward E. (MS), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_631 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Johnson, Edward James [Eddie J.] (TX) Executed June 17 1997, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_632 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Johnson, Emanuel (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_633 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Johnson, Erskine (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_634 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Johnson, Gregory S. (IN), 1992; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_635 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Johnson, James (MO), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_636 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Johnson, Joe (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_637 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Johnson, Laverne (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_638 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Johnson, Malcolm Rent (OK), 1993; 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_639 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Johnson, Mark David (OK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_640 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Johnson, Marvin (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_641 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Johnson, Richard (SC), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_642 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Johnson, Roderick A. (PA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_643 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Johnson, Ronnie (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_644 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Johnson, Vincent (OK), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_645 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Johnson, Willie Darnell (CA), 1993; 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_646 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Johnson, David (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_647 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Johnson, Timothy (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_648 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Jones, Aaron "AJ" (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_649 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Jones, Brandon Astor (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_650 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Jones, Clarence (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_651 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Jones, Claude (TX), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_652 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Jones, Damon (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_653 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Jones, Donald A. (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_654 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Jones, Earl Preston (CA), 1991; nam_apap298-1.1_655 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Jones, Gilbert (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_656 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Jones, James (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_657 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Jones, Leo A. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_658 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Jones, Raymond (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_659 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Jones, Ronald (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_660 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Jones, William R. (MO), 1993; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_661 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Joseph, Jason (VA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_662 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Joubert, John (NE), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_663 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Karis, James Leslie, Jr. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_664 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Keenan, Maurice J. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_665 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Keene, Marvellous (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_666 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Keith, David (MT), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_667 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Kennedy, Jerry (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_668 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Kennedy, Victor (AL), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_669 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Kiles, Alvie C. (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_670 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Kilgore, Bruce (MO), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_671 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Kimble, Eric B. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_672 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Kinder, Brian (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_673 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Kindler, Joseph (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_674 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - King, Amos (FL), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_675 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - King, Carolyn Ann (PA), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_676 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - King, Danny L. (VA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_677 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - King, Tommy Lee (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_678 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Kirk Patrick Jr., William (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_679 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Kitchens, William (TX), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_680 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Knapp, John (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_681 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Knight, Charles (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_682 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Knighton, Robert W. (OK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_683 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Kokal, Gregory (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_684 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Kokoraleis, Andrew (IL), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_685 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Kraft, Randy (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_686 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Kreutzer, Paul (MO), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_687 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Kvenzel, William (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_688 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Lackey, Clarence (TX), 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_689 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Lafevers, Lloyd (OK), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_690 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Laird, Richard (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_691 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Lamb, Michael (TX), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_692 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Lambert, Michael (IN), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_693 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Land, Michael Jeffrey (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_694 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Landrigan, Jeffrey (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_695 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Lang, Kenneth (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_696 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Langford, Terry A. (MT), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_697 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - LaGrand, Karl and walter (AZ) [1 of 2], 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_698 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - LaGrand, Karl and walter (AZ) [2 of 2], 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_699 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - LaRette, Anthony Joe (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_700 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Lark, Robert (PA), 1994; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_701 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Larzelere, Virginia (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_702 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Lauti, Aua (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_703 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Lawrence, John (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_704 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Lawrie, David (DE), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_705 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Lawson, David (NC) Executed June 16, 1994, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_706 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Lawton, Stacey (TX), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_707 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Lee, Chad Alan (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_708 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Lee, Darrell (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_709 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Lee, Donna (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_710 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Leisure, David (MO), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_711 (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Leisure, David (MO), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_712 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Leonard, Eric Royce (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_713 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lesko, John Charles (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_714 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Lester, Emmanuel (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_715 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Letner, Richard (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_716 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Lewis, Albert (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_717 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Lewis, John Irving (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_718 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Lewis, Reginald (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_719 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Lightbourn, Ian (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_720 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Lightsey, Christopher Charles (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_721 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Lingar, Stanley (MO), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_722 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Lipham, William Anthony (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_723 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Little, William (TX), 2004; nam_apap298-1.1_724 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Livaditis, Steven (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_725 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Livingston, Charlie (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_726 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Logan, Ronald (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_727 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Lonchar, Larry (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_728 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Long, David (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_729 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Long, Michael Edward (OK), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_730 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Lopez, Eduardo (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_731 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Lorraine, Charles (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_732 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Lovell, Ivan (MD), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_733 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Loving, Dwight J. (Military), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_734 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Lovitt, Robin (VA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_735 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Lowenfield, Leslie (LA), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_736 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Lowery, Jim (IN), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_737 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Lucas, Cecil (SC), 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_738 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Lucas, David Allen (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_739 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Lucas, Henry (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_740 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Lucero, Phillip (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_741 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Lucky, Darnell (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_742 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Lundgren, Jeffrey (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_743 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Lynch, Franklin (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_744 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Mack, Jimmy (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_745 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Mackall, Tony (VA), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_746 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Madden, Robert (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_747 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Magwood, Billy Joe (AL), 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_748 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Maharaj, Krishna (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_749 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Majors, James (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_750 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Malicoat, James (OK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_751 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Malone, Kelvin (MO), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_752 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Malone, Kelvin Shelby (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_753 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Malvo, John (VA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_754 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Mann, Fletcher Thomas (TX) Executed June 1, 1995, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_755 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Mann, Larry (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_756 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Manning, Warren (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_757 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Manriquez, Abelino (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_758 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Marek, John (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_759 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Marks, Delaney (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_760 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Marlow, James G. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_761 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Marshall, Jerry (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_762 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Marshall, Jerome (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_763 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Martin, James Lewis (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_764 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Martin, Leslie (LA), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_765 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Martin, Nollie Lee (FL), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_766 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Martinez, Alexander Rey (TX), 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_767 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Martinez-Villareal, Ramon (AZ), 1997; 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_768 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Massie, Robert Lee (CA), 2001; 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_769 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Mason, Thomas (TX), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_770 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Mata, Luis (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_771 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Matheney, Alan L. (IN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_772 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Mathenia, Charles L. (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_773 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Matthews, Earl (SC), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_774 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Matthews, Kevin, aka Al Peoples (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_775 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Maturana, Claude Eric (AZ), 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_776 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Maxwell, William (AR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_777 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Maye, Cory (MS), 2006; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_778 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Mayfield, Demetrie (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_779 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Maynard, Anson (NC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_780 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Maurer, Donald (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_781 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - McBride, Michael (TX), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_782 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - McCall, Edward (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_783 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - McCarthy, Curtis (OK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_784 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - McClain, Herbert Jr. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_785 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - McConnell, Robert (NV), 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_786 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - McCullum, Thomas (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_787 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - McDermott, Maureen (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_788 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - McFadden, Jerry (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_789 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - McFarland, Frank (TX), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_790 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - McGahee, Earl Jerome (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_791 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - McGinn, Ricky (TX), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_792 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - McGinnis, Glen Charles (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_793 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - McGowan, James (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_794 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - McKinney, James (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_795 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - McNair, Willie (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_796 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - McNeil, Christopher (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_797 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - McPeters, Ronald Avery (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_798 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - McQueen, Harold (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_799 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - McVeigh, Timothy (FED), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_800 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - McWilliams, James (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_801 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Medina, Efren (AZ), 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_802 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Medina, Pedro (FL), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_803 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Medina, Teofilo (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_804 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Medlock, Floyd (OK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_805 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Medlock, Floyd (TX), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_806 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Meeks, Douglas (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_807 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Melson, Robert Bryant (AL), 1996; nam_apap298-1.1_808 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Melton, James Andrew (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_809 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Memro, Reno (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_810 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Mendoza, Manuel (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_811 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Mendyk, Todd (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_812 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Merck, Troy (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_813 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Messiah, Keith (LA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_814 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Mickey, Douglas (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_815 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Mickle, Danny (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_816 (Box 6, Folder 105)